If we really want to blow this up,
we should involve the imperial court.
As long as the court steps in,
it will definitely be exposed.
You are being too naive.
Business on the Bian River has been going on for years.
Officials and merchants collude for profit.
Have you ever thought
that if officials turn a blind eye,
it'll all come to nothing?
What if the victims
are imperial officials?
For instance,
among the abducted women,
there are family members of high-ranking officials?
Family members of high-ranking officials?
Do you think you can scheme against them so easily?
The family members of a high-ranking official...
Isn't it right in front of us?
I have a question,
how do we get over this high wall?
Let's go, sister.
I'm troubling you again, sister.
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
Sister,
after we go out later,
we'll do this.
Okay.
You are indeed very thorough, sister.
I'll go on ahead.
See you at the restaurant.
Sir,
what would you like to eat?
Please come in.
Master.
I didn't see anyone,
but there is a letter.
How dare you, Chu Sanniang.
You want to drag me to die with you.
Sister.
Let's go over there too.
Miss Zhao.
You have a keen eye, Master Zhou.
I am indeed Zhao Han.
Thank you, Master Zhou, for escorting my aunt home today.
I often hear Sister Chu mention
that in the Imperial City Department,
you take great care of her.
Sister Chu and I are as close as sisters.
So to you, Master Zhou,
I am also deeply grateful.
In the past,
when Brother Chu Yi saved His Majesty,
he saved me as well.
Now that Brother Chu Yi is gone,
this kindness,
I can only repay it
to Sanniang.
But regarding this matter,
I am
willing but powerless.
My lady, why
not ask Layman Li to help tomorrow?
Mr. Zhou, I'm afraid we can't wait until tomorrow.
Now,
both you and Sister Chu are doomed.
Don't tell me
you still don't know what our enemy's goal is.
Have someone move the boxes away.
After the merchant ships dock, to get to Yunxiang Pavilion
and transport goods,
this is the only way.
Just now,
hearing what Mr. Zhou said,
I suppose
you also know who is behind this.
Then may I ask, Mr. Zhou,
Sister Chu is just a supervisor of the Ice Well Bureau
and a woman.
Even if the entire Chu family is included,
are they worth that person planning such a big scheme?
Isn't this using a sledgehammer to crack a nut?
I think
in this game,
their real target is...
It is the one managing the Emperor's excursions,
Director Tong of the Palace Administration.
If any mishap befalls the Emperor,
the Palace Administration will be held accountable.
But Director Tong
has great merit for suppressing the rebellion,
and he is not in the capital.
If an accident truly happens to the Emperor,
he will only be blamed for lax management.
His merits will simply offset his faults.
Then this final blow,
besides Sister Chu bearing it,
will probably only fall on you.
What crime was Supervisor Chu framed for?
Colluding with rebels,
intending
to harm the Emperor.
Meng Xiao'er.
Liu Heizi.
Meng Xiao'er, you even found helpers.
I'm not you.
I don't know the bone-shrinking skill.
Weren't you caught? How did you escape?
You're allowed to break out in the chaos,
but I'm not?
You wait.
After I finish this big business,
I'll skin you alive.
Big business?
What big business are you doing at the dock?
Why didn't you stay in Sangjia Wazi?
Your analysis is reasonable, my lady.
Then presumably,
you already have
a way to break this deadlock.
Please,
enlighten me.
Duke Tong's rival
is now extremely powerful.
Right now, the only one who can deal with him
is probably the Emperor.
The Emperor?
If you have enough evidence,
I am willing to help.
But if not,
then say no more.
Uncle Chai.
Meng Qian.
You're allowed to do big business,
but I can't receive wealthy clients?
Let me tell you,
after tonight,
once the Master of Wuyou Cave dies,
I will definitely be more famous than you.
What Dongjing Geography Ghost?
Bah!
Wuyou City.
There is evidence,
but we need
Eunuch Zhou's help to get it.
What do you mean?
Eunuch Zhou just needs to get a letter written by him,
and we'll naturally have the evidence.
A letter.
I can get that done when I go back.
However,
I wonder what crime
you plan to frame him for, my lady.
What do you think
of treason, Eunuch Zhou?
What do you think?
Treason?
Let alone His Majesty,
even I wouldn't believe it.
Then what about
colluding with His Highness the Crown Prince?
How about that?
What?
The current Crown Prince
was backed by Liang Shicheng.
If His Majesty meets a mishap and the prince ascends the throne,
who could shake
Liang Shicheng's position?
You want to drag the Crown Prince into this?
You're too bold.
Don't worry, Eunuch Zhou.
The Crown Prince's position is not what it used to be.
It is unshakeable.
Even if His Majesty wants to touch him,
the officials won't agree.
Since the Crown Prince is untouchable,
who do you think
His Majesty will vent
his anger on?
You are brilliant, my lady.
Then,
I will go back and make arrangements.
Once the letter is written,
Director Chu can see His Majesty tonight.
By the way, Director Chu.
I remember the Chu family has a gold medal bestowed by the Emperor.
Don't forget to bring it.
Wait, Eunuch Zhou.
It might be inappropriate to enter the palace tonight.
Why not wait until tomorrow?
Why is that?
Without seeing the blade,
how can treason be proven?
And how could we claim a great merit?
Alright.
I will follow your arrangements, my lady.
Let me go!
What kind of hero does this?
Fight me one-on-one if you have the guts!
Tell me,
what do you mean the Master of Wuyou Cave is dead?